[
  {
    "question": "🇸🇦",
    "response": "السعودية"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇺🇸",
    "response": "الولايات المتحدة"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇦",
    "response": "كندا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇬🇧",
    "response": "المملكة المتحدة"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇫🇷",
    "response": "فرنسا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇩🇪",
    "response": "ألمانيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇮🇹",
    "response": "إيطاليا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇪🇸",
    "response": "إسبانيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇷🇺",
    "response": "روسيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇳",
    "response": "الصين"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇯🇵",
    "response": "اليابان"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇦🇺",
    "response": "أستراليا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇮🇳",
    "response": "الهند"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇧🇷",
    "response": "البرازيل"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇦🇷",
    "response": "الأرجنتين"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇴",
    "response": "كولومبيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇲🇽",
    "response": "المكسيك"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇪🇬",
    "response": "مصر"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇹🇷",
    "response": "تركيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇬🇷",
    "response": "اليونان"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇭",
    "response": "سويسرا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇷🇴",
    "response": "رومانيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇵🇱",
    "response": "بولندا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇷🇸",
    "response": "صربيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇸🇪",
    "response": "السويد"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇳🇴",
    "response": "النرويج"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇩🇰",
    "response": "الدنمارك"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇳🇱",
    "response": "هولندا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇧🇪",
    "response": "بلجيكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇦🇹",
    "response": "النمسا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇿",
    "response": "التشيك"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇭🇺",
    "response": "هنغاريا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇵🇹",
    "response": "البرتغال"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇵🇪",
    "response": "بيرو"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇨🇱",
    "response": "تشيلي"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇻🇪",
    "response": "فنزويلا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇿🇦",
    "response": " أفريقيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇪🇹",
    "response": "إثيوبيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇪🇨",
    "response": "الإكوادور"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇳🇿",
    "response": "نيوزيلندا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇳🇬",
    "response": "نيجيريا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇩🇿",
    "response": "الجزائر"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇲🇦",
    "response": "المغرب"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇹🇳",
    "response": "تونس"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇪🇬",
    "response": "مصر"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇱🇧",
    "response": "لبنان"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇯🇴",
    "response": "الأردن"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇸🇾",
    "response": "سوريا"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇮🇶",
    "response": "العراق"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇶🇦",
    "response": "قطر"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇦🇪",
    "response": "الإمارات"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇰🇼",
    "response": "الكويت"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇴🇲",
    "response": "عمان"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇧🇭",
    "response": "البحرين"
  },
  {
    "question": "🇾🇪",
    "response": "اليمن"
  }
]
